# **EOIN MCLAUGHLIN**

### PERSONAL DETAILS

Email Address: <a href="mailto:eoinmclaway@gmail.com">eoinmclaway@gmail.com</a>

Contact Number: 07456613387

National Insurance Number: Can be provided upon request

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I have excellent organizational and communication skills which I have developed and use to provide excellent customer service in a busy bar environment. With the experience I have gained from working in a bar environment, I can perform and excel both working individually or as part of the team.

#### **SKILLS**

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Computer Skills
- Adaptable

# PREVIOUS EMPLOYMENT

St Paul's GAC Sports Bar - Bar Staff	January 2015 – November 2017
Féile An Phobail - Bar Staff	August 2017 & 2018
Amadeus - Casual Multi Skilled Operative (Formerly)	October 2017 – May 2018
Hospitality Belfast - Casual Multi Skilled Operative	May 2018 - Ongoing
Waterfront Hall and Ulster Hall	
Sodexo – Casual Work Staff	August 2018 – September 2018
Carphone Warehouse - Customer Service Assistant	October 2018 - Ongoing
HSC Business Services Organisation - 1 Week Work Experience	ge January 2017
EIR NI -1 Week Work Experience	January 2016

### QUALIFICATIONS

7 GCSE'S (Grade A-C) August 2015

ncluding Maths and English

August 2016 & 2017

3 AS Levels (Grade B-D)

• Including Digital Technology and Sports Science

3 A Levels (Grade CCD)

August 2018

I

I

ncluding Moving Image Arts, Digital Technology and Sports Science

Duke of Edinburgh Bronze Award

June 2013

#### HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

My major hobby is sport. I currently play Gaelic Football for school and club, while playing this I have developed many relationships with people from other clubs, counties and sports. However, from a young age I've had a huge interest in technology and computers. As I've got older this interest kept developing persuading me to follow a career in IT as well as my interest in technology. I have kept up to date on the new technology releases from headphones to mobile phones. I have a keen interest in photography and videography. This gives me a form of expression that I previously didn't have and it has allowed me to achieve many different things which I was unable to achieve before. It has also given me different opportunities that I previously wouldn't have achieved. Combining these, it has given me the ability to be driven to achieve many things together with a team and individually. I have a huge interest in technology especially computers where I learned a lot of what I know today. With this interest I have achieved some of my personal goals which include building my own computer and the network in my house.

## REFERENCES

Can be provided upon request